

Federico Irarrazaval

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



About me

I am proactive and disciplined.

My academic and employment experience have always oriented me to deliver customer-oriented and high quality products and services.

Technologies

JavaScript | Typescript | Node.js Express.js | Fastify | Koa.js | JSON API's MongoDB | Mongoose PostgreSQL | Sequelize | HTML5 React | Redux CSS | Chakra UI Railway | Heroku Vercel | Shopify Canva | Trello | Vtex IO

Skills

- Team work | SCRUM methodology
- Developed soft skills
- Advanced English proficiency (C2 Proficient)

Hobbies

I enjoy my reading, as well as technology and gamming.

I am also interested in sports. Currently practicing archery.

Contact Me











December 1, 2023

Experience

ITGlobers - Back End Developer

February 2023 - Present

Back end developer for marketplaces and e-commerce projects working with Typescript, Node.js, Express.js, Koa.js, API's, and VTEX IO.

Henry - Full Stack Developer

Kinema Project (2022)

4 weeks team academic experience under SCRUM methodology. I collaborated as full stack developer.

Kinema is a movie and tv shows streaming website built with the following technologies: Javascript, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Moongose, React, Redux, Chakra UI, CSS, Cloudinary, Firebase, Stripe, Email.js, Railway and Vercel.

Kinema was selected by Henry bootcamp among the top 4 projects of the course.

@ Gaming & Beyond Project (2022)

4 weeks academic experience.

G&B is a videogame browser website built according to clean architecture principles and with the following technologies: Typescript, Javascript, fastify, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, React, Redux and CSS. Deployed with Railway and Vercel.

Academic experience

Bootcamp Full Stack Web Developer

Henry, 2022

1000 hours of courses and practice with the following technologies: Javascript, Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, API's, React, Redux, HTML and CSS..

Programming Courses

- Course "Typescript POO and asynchronism". Platzi, 2023
- Course "Backend with node.js. Authentication with passport.js and jwt".
 Platzi, 2023
- Course "Practice Node.js: Authentication". Platzi, 2023
- Course "Typescript. Fundamentals". Platzi, 2023
- Course "Typescript. Advanced types and functions". Platzi, 2023
- Course "Node.js. Fundamentals. Platzi, 2023
- Course "Backend with Node.js: API REST with express.js". Platzi, 2023
- Course "Programming with Python". Píldoras Informaticas, 2021
- Curso "Python for non-programmers". EducaciónIT, 2021
- Course "Programming Foundations: Fundamentals". LinkedIn Learning, 2021

Employment background

Sr. Attorney

Baker McKenzie, 2015 - 2022

Labour & Employment law advise and litigation for local and foreign companies. Led several teams of paralegals and junior attorneys.

Jr. Attorney

Mansueti, Gallo & Sallete, 2015 Labour & Employment law advice.

Academic background

Specialization on Labour & Employment Law

Pontifical Catholic University of Argentina, 2018 - 2020

Labour & Employment Law Postgraduate Course

Pontifical Catholic University of Argentina, 2016

Corporate Legal Advice Postgraduate Course

Pontifical Catholic University of Argentina, 2015

Law Degree

Pontifical Catholic University of Argentina, 2006 - 2014

Bachelor's Degree

Los Molinos School, 1994 - 2006